<resources>
    <string name="app_name">SnowboardTrickGuide</string>

    <!-- questions to ask the user -->
    <!-- questions for aerial part of tree -->
    <string name="category_q_text">Pick a category</string>
    <string name="approach_stance_q_text">What stance is the trick approached on?</string>
    <string name="any_spins_q_text">Were any spins performed?</string>
    <string name="rotation_direction_q_text">What direction of rotation?</string>
    <string name="many_spins_q_text">How many degrees of rotation are performed in the air before landing?</string>
    <string name="grab_performed_q_text">Was a grab performed in the air?</string>
    <string name="select_grab_q_text">What grab?</string>
    <string name="shifty_performed_q_text">Was a shifty performed while in the air?</string>
    <string name="inversion_performed_q_text">Was there any inversion?</string>
    <string name="inversion_dir_q_text">Direction of inversion?</string>
    <string name="num_flips_q_text">Number of flips?</string>
    <string name="pop_used_q_text">What pop is used to get off the ground?</string>

    <!-- questions for jib part of tree -->
    <string name="type_of_jib_q_text">What type of jib?</string>
    <string name="type_of_feature_q_text">What type of feature is the trick done on?</string>
    <string name="side_of_feature_approach_q_text">What direction is the feature approached on?</string>
    <string name="rotation_on_less_180_q_text">Is the rotation getting onto the feature less than a full 180 degree turn?</string>
    <string name="type_slide_on_feature_q_text">What way is the board initially on the feature?</string>
    <string name="press_performed_on_feature_q_text">Is a press performed while on the feature?</string>
    <string name="type_press_q_text">What type of press?</string>
    <string name="rotation_off_more_180_q_text">Is an about 180 degree rotation or more performed while coming off of the feature?</string>
    <string name="tap_performed_out_q_text">Is a tail or nose tap performed while coming off of the feature?</string>
    <string name="nose_tail_tap_out_q_text">Is the feature tapped with the nose or the tail?</string>
    <string name="part_board_on_top_feature_q_text">What part of the board is on top of the feature?</string>
    <string name="rotation_off_90_less_q_text">Is the rotation after coming off of the feature about 90 degrees or less?</string>
    <string name="position_landed_off_feature_q_text">What way is the trick landed after coming off the feature?</string>
    <string name="rotation_off_270_q_text">Is the rotation after coming off of the feature about 270 degrees?</string>
    <string name="rotation_same_opposite_q_text">Is the direction of rotation the same or opposite direction of rotation of the previous move?</string>
    <string name="select_rotation_amount_off_q_text">Which amount of rotation is about what is performed coming off of the feature?</string>
    <string name="select_rotation_amount_on_q_text">Which amount of rotation is about what is performed getting onto the feature?</string>
    <string name="board_pass_over_feature_q_text">Does the front or the back of the board pass over the feature first?</string>
    <string name="more_180_continued_on_feature_q_text">Is more than a 180 degree spin continued while on the feature?</string>
    <string name="total_spins_q_text">How many spins in total were performed from start to beginning of the trick?</string>
    <string name="spins_before_feature_q_text">How many spins are performed in the air before landing on the feature?</string>
    <string name="spins_after_feature_q_text">How many spins are performed in the air after getting off the feature?</string>
    <string name="before_stall_feature_180_q_text">Is a 180 degree rotation done in the air before hitting the stall on the feature?</string>
    <string name="after_stall_feature_180_q_text">Is a 180 degree rotation done just after stalling on the feature?</string>
    <string name="board_contact_feature_stall_q_text">What part of the board is in contact to the feature when fully stalled on the feature?</string>
    <string name="press_back_foot_stall_q_text">Is a press over the trailing foot performed while stalled?</string>
    <string name="feature_tapped_q_text">What type of feature is being tapped?</string>
    <string name="feature_q_text">What feature?</string>

    <!-- questions for the butter part of the tree -->
    <string name="board_on_off_ground_q_text">Does the board stay on the ground through during the trick or gets off the ground?</string>
    <string name="side_board_pressed_q_text">Which side of the board is being pressed at the beginning of the trick?</string>
    <string name="any_rotation_q_text">Is any rotation performed during this trick?</string>
    <string name="pause_90_q_text">Is there a pause in the rotation at about 90 degrees of rotation?</string>
    <string name="either_90_or_270_opposite_q_text">Is the rotation after the pause: 90 degrees in either direction or 270 degrees in the opposite direction?</string>
    <string name="last_90_rotation_direction_q_text">Is the last 90 degree rotation the same or opposite direction of the last rotation?</string>
    <string name="many_spins_in_press_q_text">How many degrees of rotation are preformed while pressed?</string>
    <string name="either_90_or_270_same_q_text">Is the rotation after the pause: 90 degrees in either direction or 270 degrees in the same direction?</string>
    <string name="hands_on_ground_behind_q_text">Are one or both hands being put on the ground behind the board?</string>
    <string name="hands_ground_back_leg_extended_q_text">Does the back leg stay extended when the hands are on the ground or bent?</string>
    <string name="hands_ground_some_point_q_text">Are one or both hands on the ground at some point in this trick?</string>
    <string name="rotation_180_or_360_q_text">Is a 180 degree or 360 degree rotation made during this trick?</string>
    <string name="rotation_90_less_q_text">Is the rotation done about 90 degrees or less, including no rotation?</string>
    <string name="approached_up_incline_q_text">Is the trick approached going up an incline and performed at the top of transitioning back down it?</string>
    <string name="nose_press_grabbing_tail_q_text">Is the nose of the board pressed hard into the ground and the back hand grabbing anywhere around the tail?</string>
    <string name="tail_press_grabbing_nose_q_text">Is the tail of the board pressed hard into the ground and the front hand grabbing anywhere around the nose?</string>

    <!-- button names -->
    <string name="aerial_button_text">Aerial</string>
    <string name="jibb_button_text">Jib</string>
    <string name="butter_button_text">Butter</string>
    <string name="other_button_text">Other</string>

    <string name="switch_button_text">Switch</string>
    <string name="natural_button_text">Natural</string>
    <string name="skip_button_text">Skip</string>

    <string name="yes_button_text">Yes</string>
    <string name="no_button_text">No</string>

    <string name="ollie_button_text">Ollie</string>
    <string name="nollie_button_text">Nollie</string>
    <string name="straight_button_text">Straight</string>

    <string name="frontside_button_text">Frontside</string>
    <string name="backside_button_text">Backside</string>
    <string name="straight_on_button_text">Straight On</string>
    <string name="no_rotation_button_text">No Rotation</string>

    <string name="front_button_text">Front</string>
    <string name="back_button_text">Back</string>

    <string name="slide_button_text">Slide</string>
    <string name="stall_button_text">Stall</string>
    <string name="tap_button_text">Tap</string>

    <string name="box_button_text">Box</string>
    <string name="rail_button_text">Rail</string>
    <string name="pipe_button_text">Pipe</string>

    <string name="fifty_fifty_button_text">50-50</string>
    <string name="boardslide_button_text">Boardslide</string>
    <string name="lipslide_button_text">Lipslide</string>

    <string name="tail_press_button_text">Tail Press</string>
    <string name="nose_press_button_text">Nose Press</string>

    <string name="nose_button_text">Nose</string>
    <string name="tail_button_text">Tail</string>

    <string name="leading_foot_button_text">Leading Foot</string>
    <string name="trailing_foot_button_text">Trailing Foot</string>
    <string name="inbetween_feet_button_text">In between Feet</string>

    <string name="same_button_text">Same</string>
    <string name="opposite_button_text">Opposite</string>

    <string name="num_450_button_text">450</string>
    <string name="num_630_button_text">630</string>
    <string name="num_180_button_text">180</string>
    <string name="num_270_button_text">270</string>
    <string name="num_90_button_text">90</string>
    <string name="num_360_button_text">360</string>

    <string name="on_the_ground_button_text">On the ground</string>
    <string name="off_the_ground_button_text">Off the ground</string>

    <string name="extended_button_text">Extended</string>
    <string name="bent_button_text">Bent</string>

    <string name="select_button_text">Select</string>

    <string name="save_button_text">Save</string>
    <string name="continue_button_text">Continue</string>

    <string name="restart_button_text">Restart</string>

    <string name="complete_button_text">Complete</string>
    <string name="close_button_text">Close</string>

    <string name="shorten_button_text">Shorten</string>
    <string name="lengthen_button_text">Lengthen</string>
    <string name="try_again_button_text">Try again</string>

    <string name="important_button_text">Important</string>

    <string name="ok_button_text">OK</string>
    <string name="order_button_text">Order</string>

    <string name="find_trick_button_text">Define And Find a Trick</string>

    <string name="tricks_completed_button_text">Tricks Completed</string>
    <string name="tricks_to_do_button_text">Tricks To Do</string>
    <string name="cancel_button_text">Cancel</string>
    <string name="replace_button_text">Replace</string>

    <string name="credits_button_text">Credits</string>
    <string name="your_stats_button_text">Your Stats</string>
    <string name="learn_button_text">Learn</string>
    <string name="important_terminology_button_text">Important Terminology</string>
    <string name="helpful_links_button_text">Helpful Links</string>
    <string name="understanding_defining_a_trick_button_text">Understanding Defining A Trick</string>
    <string name="email_me_button_text">Email Me</string>

    <!-- text for the question answers with too many selections to warrent a branch for each option -->
    <string name="select_spins_text">Select number in increments of 180 degree rotations.</string>
    <string name="select_grab_text">Select an available grab using the image below or type it in if you cannot find it.</string>
    <string name="select_feature_text">Select an available feature or type it in if not found.</string>

    <!-- Parts of trick names that are not a buttons text -->
    <string name="cab_trick">Cab</string>
    <string name="tamedog_trick">Tamedog</string>
    <string name="wildcat_trick">Wildcat</string>
    <string name="fakie_trick">Fakie</string>

    <!-- descriptions for page options -->
    <string name="category_description_text">
        Choose the category of trick that the trick you are looking for falls under.
    </string>
    <string name="feature_description_text">
        Choose a feature that describes what the trick was performed on. The 3 most common features
        are boxes, rails, and pipes. Boxes will have a flat, white-ish top. Rails are most always
        metal and thin, similar to the handrails of a staircase. Pipes (or tubes) have a hollow
        middle. Features come in a practically endless variety of shapes and positions so if you
        have a more specific name for the feature, select Other and type in it.
    </string>
    <string name="aerial_description_text">
        A trick performed where the snowboard lifts off the ground off of an allocated jump with a
        ramp.
    </string>
    <string name="butter_description_text">
        A trick that can be performed on flat ground or off mellow hills, often starting with the
        snowboarders weight over the nose or tail of the snowboard.
    </string>
    <string name="jib_description_text">
        A trick that is performed across a surface that is not snow, such as rails, boxes, trees,
        etc.
    </string>

    <string name="butter_continue_description_text">
        The great thing about butter tricks is that you can almost always connect multiple
        butter tricks together as long as they are all performed in one fluid motion. Endless possibilities!
        If this trick is not the last one performed of a combination butter trick, click CONTINUE to chain on
        another trick. Press Try again to restart this search. Press Complete if this is the full trick.
    </string>
    <string name="trick_discovered_description_text">
        Press the SAVE button to save this trick as shown above to the My Trick List or to the
        Tricks To Do List. You can get the shorter and more slangy name of the trick by pressing
        Shorten. If this was not the trick you were looking for, you can press Try again or exit.
    </string>
    <string name="stance_approach_description_text">
        This question refers whether the rider is starting the trick in their dominant and most
        comfortable stance (Natural) or their non-dominant (Switch). A stance can have either foot leading down the slope:
        the left foot called Regular or the right foot called Goofy. If you are not sure if the trick starts
        Natural or Switch, or it is irrelevant, click Skip.
    </string>
    <string name="spins_performed_description_text">
        Select Yes if there is at least a full 180 degrees of rotation (half a full rotation)
        done from the moment right before going airborne to when the trick is landed. This is the
        amount of rotation of the board.
    </string>
    <string name="rotation_direction_description_text">
        Direction of rotation is one of two ways, defined by what side of the body of the rider is facing down the hill in the first
        90 degrees of rotation: the front of the body (Frontside) or the back of the body (Backside).
    </string>
    <string name="inversion_performed_description_text">
        An inversion is defined as the head being below the head of the rider. If at any point while
        in the air this is true, select Yes.
    </string>
    <string name="inversion_direction_description_text">
        The inversion direction can have either the head going back behind the body (Back) or
        the head going in front of the body (Front).
    </string>
    <string name="pop_description_text">
        Pop is describing the way the rider uses the board to jump off the ground. They can transfer
        their weight over their back foot, springing off the tail of the board (Ollie). They can transfer
        their weight over their front foot, springing off the nose of the board (Nollie). They can
        have their weight centered over the board, jumping with the board flat on the ground (Straight).
        If you are not sure or it is irrelevant to this trick, select Straight.
    </string>
    <string name="grab_performed_description_text">
        A grab is the act of grabbing the board with one of either hands or both at the same time while airborne.
    </string>
    <string name="grab_description_text">
        Use the image to select the an available grab or if it is not an option select Other to type one in.
    </string>
    <string name="shifty_description_text">
        A shifty is the act of counter rotating the board separate of the riders body while in the air and
        bringing the counter rotation back to the proper position being landing.
    </string>

    <string name="jib_type_description_text">
        A Slide is literally sliding across a feature from one end to the other. A Stall is approaching
        a feature on a slight incline and stopping on that feature and coming off the feature back down the side
        it was approached on, similar to the act of going up and down the side of a halfpipe. A Tap is
        jumping over a feature and quickly hitting the feature with the board while passing it.
    </string>
    <string name="tap_board_description_text">
        The Nose is the leading end of the board. The Tail is the trailing end of the board. If you
        are not sure what it is or it is irrelevant, select Skip.
    </string>
    <string name="side_feature_approached_description_text">
        The way a feature is approached is defined by what way the feature is facing the rider.
        The feature in front of the rider (Frontside) or the feature to the back of the rider (Backside)
        or going straight at the feature (Straight On).
    </string>
    <string name="stall_contact_description_text">
        When fully stopped on the feature, is the board in contact to the feature in between the rider
        feet/bindings (In between Feet), or on or past the riders back foot (Trailing Foot). The back foot
        being the foot going uphill.
    </string>
    <string name="rotation_onto_feature_description_text">
        This is asking about the rotation done in between the moment the board leaves the snow to the moment
        the rider lands on the feature. Also the rotation is about the boards movement, the rotation or
        lack rotation of the rider themselves is irrelevant.
    </string>
    <string name="rotation_off_feature_description_text">
        This is asking about the rotation done in between the moment the board leaves the feature to
        the moment the rider lands back on the snow. Also the rotation is about the boards movement, the rotation or
        lack rotation of the rider themselves is irrelevant.
    </string>
    <string name="after_stall_rotation_description_text">
        This question is asking about the rotation of the board itself from the moment the board gets
        off of the feature to when the board lands back on the snow. It does not count as a 180 rotation
        unless the board is riding away straight and not on an edge.
    </string>
    <string name="press_stall_description_text">
        Answer Yes if the rider transfers their weight over their foot on the uphill side while on the feature.
        It will also look like the rider is poking the nose of their board over the feature.
    </string>
    <string name="type_slide_description_text">
        The rider can get on a feature 3 different ways: on the feature without any rotation and riding on
        it straight with the board in contact with the feature along the entire length of itself (50-50),
        a slight rotation about 90 degrees where the front/leading end of the board goes over the feature and the
        board is sliding perpendicular on the feature (Boardslide), or a slight rotation about 90 degrees
        where the back/trailing end of the board goes over the feature and the board is sliding perpendicular
        on the feature (Lipslide).
    </string>
    <string name="select_rotation_180_270_description_text">
        Answers in degrees of rotation and it about the amount of rotation of the riders board, regardless of
        the riders body. 180 being a half a full rotation and 270 three quarters of one. If it is clearly
        not a 180 degree rotation but not exactly a 270, select 270 as it can be not exactly 270 degrees.
    </string>
    <string name="press_description_text">
        A press can be on the nose, the leading end of the board (Front), or the tail, the trailing end of the
        board(Back). It is performed when the riders weight is transferred over the nose (Nose Press) or the
        tail (Tail Press). The opposite end of the board should be off the ground if properly pressed.
    </string>
    <string name="part_board_feature_description_text">
        According to the foot positioning of the rider at the start of the trick before jumping off the
        snow to get on the feature, the board could have the feature under the leading foot, over the
        trailing foot, or in between the feet/bindings. Note if it is over the leading foot or the
        trailing foot, the rider weight should be transferred over said foot.
    </string>
    <string name="board_pass_over_description_text">
        According to the foot positioning of the rider at the start of the trick before jumping off the
        snow to get on the feature, it can be the front/leading foot (Front) or the back/trailing foot
        (Back).
    </string>
    <string name="spin_continued_on_feature_description_text">
        This spin must have the rotation done while on the feature and be at least half a full rotation.
        The board will stay in contact with the feature through the spins. This continual spinning
        while on the feature is most commonly and easily done on a box feature, but it is possible
        on other features.
    </string>
    <string name="stance_landed_description_text">
        This question refers whether the rider ends the trick in their dominant and most
        comfortable stance (Natural) or their non-dominant (Switch). A stance have either foot leading down the slope:
        the left foot called Regular or the right foot called Goofy. If you are not sure if the trick ends
        Natural or Switch, or it is irrelevant, click Skip.
    </string>
    <string name="tap_off_description_text">
        This would involve jumping off the feature just before reaching the end and while in the air
        using one end of the board to literally hit the feature. The can be done with the front/leading
        end of the board (Nose) or the back/trailing end of the board (Tail).
    </string>
    <string name="same_opposite_rotation_description_text">
        This only has to do with the boards rotation, the riders body is irrelevant. You will have
        the board make a rotation getting onto the feature. Is the next act of rotation the same
        or the opposite direction of that first act of rotation.
    </string>

    <string name="on_off_ground_description_text">
        Remember if you are finding a trick that has more than one butter trick done in the full motion,
        you are only answering this question according to the single part of the full trick you are
        describing. This is important because the trick can involve one of the trick done while with the board in contact with the
        ground and the another with the board coming off the ground.
    </string>
    <string name="any_rotation_description_text">
        Remember if you are finding a trick that has more than one butter trick done in the full motion,
        you are only answering this question according to the single part of the full trick you are
        describing. This is important because the trick can involve one of the trick done without any rotation
        and the another with rotation. Also rotation refers only to the boards rotation, the riders body is irrelevant.
    </string>
    <string name="pause_at_90_description_text">
        If Yes, the first move of this specific butter will be 90 degrees of rotation followed by a clear period of
        time with no rotation after the initial 90 degrees. Remember the rotation refers only to the boards rotation,
        the riders body is irrelevant.
    </string>
    <string name="back_leg_extended_description_text">
        The back leg is the trailing leg or the leg on the uphill side of the slope at the time of
        preforming this trick.
    </string>
    <string name="up_incline_description_text">
        Similar to the way a trick is performed at the top of a halfpipe, this will be performed in
        the process of transitioning back down the incline.
    </string>
    <string name="board_block_description_text">
        This will involve the length of the board being close to vertical when these actions are performed
        and the rider riding away after this back the way the trick was approached.
    </string>
    <string name="last_90_after_pause_description_text">
        The last rotation refers to the rotation of the initial rotation that stops at 90 degrees for
        a period of time. Answer if the following rotation is in the same or opposite direction of
        rotation.
    </string>

    <!-- the message for after clicking a category to briefly explain things with a do not show again checkbox -->
    <string name="aerial_explain_text">
        An Aerial for this apps purposes is defined as a trick where the rider is airborne and the
        trick is done off a purposefully allocated jump, so generally an artificial jump. This can include
        drop offs and side hits to your own discretion but should not include mellow hills or bumps as
        those are reserved for Butters. The start of an Aerial trick is marked by the moment just before going
        airborne and ends when the board lands back on the ground. Anything done before or after these
        two points are not a part of the trick. The start and end of the trick is important to note
        when answering future questions. Can define flatspins and inversion but not tricks that involve
        both at the same time like corks or rodeos.
    </string>

    <string name="butter_explain_text">
        A Butter for this apps purposes is defined as a trick done on flat ground or mellow hills.
        Any butter that you find in this tree is "relatively" simple and describes a single move.
        Many butter tricks are a combination of these simple tricks put back-to-back in one
        fluid motion and you will be able to chain together a combination butter in this search by defining
        each part separately. Because the trick can have multiple parts, the trick must be looked at
        closely to divide it into each move, which can be defined by a change of press, rotation, etc.
        If the board goes airborne, everything done in the air until the board is back on the ground
        defines a single move. If the riders weight is centered over the board with it flat on the ground
        for anything more than a slight moment, that marks the end of the butter trick. The trick starts
        when a press is performed or the board goes airborne.
    </string>

    <string name="jib_explain_text">
        A Jib is a trick done riding the board across a non-pisted surface AKA anything that is not snow.
        Boxes, rails, trees, houses, balls, anything. The variety of features to jib on are practically
        endless so you are given the ability to name the feature your self, but the most common features
        to find in a park are boxes and rails. Note that because the variety is endless, this search
        cannot cover everything. It covers practically any trick on standard park features, NOT including
        change-ups/switch-ups done while on the feature or any butters done on the feature other than
        a nose and tail press. The start of the trick is marked by the moment the board leaves the snow
        to get on the feature and ends when the snowboard lands back on the snow.
    </string>

    <!-- Secondary texts for errors, alerts, small texts, etc. -->
    <string name="no_description_dialog_text"> No description of this answer</string>
    <string name="hold_button_text">Try holding down on the answers to see a more detailed description of what it is</string>
    <string name="trick_discovered_greeting_text">Nice Trick! Which is called:</string>
    <string name="butter_discovered_greeting_text">This butter in full is called:</string>
    <string name="are_you_sure_rest_text">Are you sure you want to discard this search and start another one?</string>
    <string name="are_you_sure_exit_text">Are you sure you want to exit \"ADDING A TRICK\"? Any current progress will be lost.</string>
    <string name="do_not_show_again_text">Do not show this again.</string>
    <string name="no_tricks_completed_text">
        No tricks completed yet. Add a trick by pressing the button below to find a trick
        by answering a series of questions or press the top right button to add a trick manually.</string>
    <string name="no_tricks_todo_text">
        No tricks on the To Do list. Add a trick by pressing the button below to find a trick
        by answering a series of questions or press the top right button to add a trick manually.</string>
    <string name="search_trick_button_text">Search for a trick</string>
    <string name="add_trick_manually_button_text">Add trick manually</string>
    <string name="info_button_text">Info</string>
    <string name="settings_button_text">Settings</string>
    <string name="to_do_button_text">To Do</string>
    <string name="save_dialog_text">Do you want to save this trick to your Tricks Completed List or to your Tricks To Do List?</string>
    <string name="delete_selected_button_text">Delete selected</string>
    <string name="move_to_to_do_list">Move to To Do List</string>
    <string name="search_in_list_action">Search in List</string>
    <string name="move_to_completed_list">Move to Completed List</string>
    <string name="duplicate_completed_list">This trick is already saved in your Tricks Completed List. Do you want to replace it with this trick?</string>
    <string name="duplicate_todo_list">This trick is already saved in your Tricks To Do List. Do you want to replace it with this trick?</string>
    <string name="trick_name_error">Must have a full name</string>
    <string name="category_error">Must have a category</string>
    <string name="date_error">Enter a valid date</string>
    <string name="duplicate_error">This trick already exists</string>
    <string name="back_button_pressed_text">Press one more time to exit app</string>
    <string name="editor_what_list_text">Is this trick completed or something to do?</string>
    <string name="sort_list_settings_header_text">Sort lists by:</string>
    <string name="feedback_text">Find any problems, bugs, typos, things that should be added, false
        information, etc.? Email me notes, suggestions, and feedback. Please be specific about the where, when, and how?</string>
    <string name="num_tricks_info"># of tricks discovered:</string>
    <string name="num_completed_tricks_info"># of completed tricks:</string>
    <string name="num_tricks_to_do_info"># of tricks to do:</string>

    <!-- Top bar fun messages -->
    <string name="top_bar_beginning_search_text">What we hittin\'...</string>
    <string name="top_bar_search_in_tree_text">Stoke up for a sweet</string>
    <string name="top_bar_butter_found_text">Nice and buttery</string>
    <string name="top_bar_aerial_found_text">Stomped that one out</string>
    <string name="top_bar_jib_found_text">Are you a jibber or something?</string>

    <!-- keys for Intents -->
    <string name="add_regular_key">addRegular</string>
    <string name="add_replacement_key">addReplacement</string>
    <string name="edit_trick_key">editTrick</string>
    <string name="orginial_trick_key">originalTrick</string>
    <string name="updated_trick_key">updatedTrick</string>
    <string name="is_completed_key">isCompleted</string>

    <!-- keys and values for Shared Preferences -->
    <string name="sort_list_by_key">sortListBy</string>
    <string name="sort_list_order_key">sortListOrder</string>

    <string name="sort_list_by_name_value">Name</string>
    <string name="sort_list_by_category_value">Category</string>
    <string name="sort_list_by_date_value">Date</string>

    <string name="sort_list_ascending_value">Ascending</string>
    <string name="sort_list_descending_value">Descending</string>

    <!-- Content Descriptions -->
    <string name="exit_activity_cd">Exit activity without saving anything</string>
    <string name="icon_editor_title_cd">Icon for the title of the trick that will be displayed in the list</string>
    <string name="icon_alternate_name_cd">Icon for the alternate name of the trick that will not be displayed</string>
    <string name="icon_editor_category_cd">Icon for the category of this trick</string>
    <string name="icon_date_cd">Icon for the date of the trick</string>
    <string name="icon_inlist_cd">Icon for what list the trick should be in</string>
    <string name="icon_notes_cd">Icon for the extra notes on this trick</string>
    <string name="search_trick_fab_cd">Find a Trick</string>
    <string name="find_trick_cd">Go to search to find a trick by answering a series of questions</string>
    <string name="image_expand_trick_cd">Image to expand a trick to see all parts of it and possibly edit it</string>
    <string name="image_features_cd">Image with examples of common features</string>
    <string name="imagebutton_cycle_grab_cd">Cycle through available image diagrams for identifying a grab</string>
    <string name="image_grab_cd">Image of grab diagram to identify a grab</string>
    <string name="editor_delete_cd">Permanently delete this trick</string>

    <!-- Hint texts -->
    <string name="trick_name_editor_hint">Trick Name</string>
    <string name="alternate_name_editor_hint">Alternate naming of the trick</string>
    <string name="editor_category_hint">Trick category (Aerial, Jib, Butter, etc.)</string>
    <string name="editor_date_hint">Date of trick: mm/dd/yyyy</string>
    <string name="editor_notes_hint">Notes, descriptions, location, or information about this trick</string>
    <string name="feature_other_hint">Type the feature name</string>
    <string name="other_grab_hint">Type the grab name</string>

    <!-- Toast texts -->


</resources>